const Questions=[
    {question:"hi", answer:"Hello, Can I know your name"},
    {question:"good morning", answer:"Good Morning, How you doing"},
    {question:"good evening", answer:"Good evening, What's up"},
    {question:"good night", answer:"Good Night, have a nice night mate"},
    {question:"how you doing", answer:"I am doing fine, How come you knew about me"},
    {question:"what are you doing", answer:"Just giving some advices to some people"},
    {question:"fine", answer:"Good for you"},
    {question:"thank you", answer:"Pleasure"},
    {question:"what about you", answer:"I am good"},
    {question:"will you please give me a advice", answer:"Sure, tell me what happened"},
    {question:"what should i do about that", answer:"The answer is very simple, just give yourself some time and everything will be all good"},
    {question:"fine", answer:"Nice to hear that sorry I mean read thatüòÅ"},
    {question:"bye", answer:"bye, have a great day or night whatever it might beüíÄ."},
]

export  default Questions